[
    {
        "question": "略す",
        "answer": "りゃくす"
    },
    {
        "question": "担ぐ",
        "answer": "かつぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "銅",
        "answer": "どう"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒸す",
        "answer": "むす"
    },
    {
        "question": "随筆",
        "answer": "ずいひつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "回数券",
        "answer": "かいすうけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "山林",
        "answer": "さんりん"
    },
    {
        "question": "恋しい",
        "answer": "こいしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "角度",
        "answer": "かくど"
    },
    {
        "question": "矢印",
        "answer": "やじるし"
    },
    {
        "question": "損得",
        "answer": "そんとく"
    },
    {
        "question": "改正",
        "answer": "かいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "低下",
        "answer": "ていか"
    },
    {
        "question": "畳む",
        "answer": "たたむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "刺す",
        "answer": "さす"
    },
    {
        "question": "食塩",
        "answer": "しょくえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "純情",
        "answer": "じゅんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "水筒",
        "answer": "すいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "泊める",
        "answer": "とめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "延長",
        "answer": "えんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "官庁",
        "answer": "かんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "祭日",
        "answer": "さいじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾電池",
        "answer": "かんでんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "休講",
        "answer": "きゅうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "再来月",
        "answer": "さらいげつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "線路",
        "answer": "せんろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "芸能",
        "answer": "げいのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "皮膚",
        "answer": "ひふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "油断",
        "answer": "ゆだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "軟らかい",
        "answer": "やわらかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "再来年",
        "answer": "さらいねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "測る",
        "answer": "はかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "作る/造る",
        "answer": "つくる"
    },
    {
        "question": "兵隊",
        "answer": "へいたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "刷る",
        "answer": "する"
    },
    {
        "question": "寒帯",
        "answer": "かんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "光線",
        "answer": "こうせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "垣根",
        "answer": "かきね"
    },
    {
        "question": "混合",
        "answer": "こんごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "拝む",
        "answer": "おがむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "個体",
        "answer": "こたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒸気",
        "answer": "じょうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "裏口",
        "answer": "うらぐち"
    },
    {
        "question": "賞金",
        "answer": "しょうきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "腰掛け",
        "answer": "こしかけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "消防署",
        "answer": "しょうぼうしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "順序",
        "answer": "じゅんじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "片付く",
        "answer": "かたづく"
    },
    {
        "question": "耕す",
        "answer": "たがやす"
    },
    {
        "question": "基準",
        "answer": "きじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "演劇",
        "answer": "えんげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "詰まる",
        "answer": "つまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "消極的",
        "answer": "しょうきょくてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "児童",
        "answer": "じどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "方針",
        "answer": "ほうしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "全般",
        "answer": "ぜんぱん"
    },
    {
        "question": "対照",
        "answer": "たいしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "総理大臣",
        "answer": "そうりだいじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "漁業",
        "answer": "ぎょぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "効力",
        "answer": "こうりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "四角い",
        "answer": "しかくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "鑑賞",
        "answer": "かんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "荒い",
        "answer": "あらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "農薬",
        "answer": "のうやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "肌着",
        "answer": "はだぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "祭る",
        "answer": "まつる"
    },
    {
        "question": "延びる",
        "answer": "のびる"
    },
    {
        "question": "免税",
        "answer": "めんぜい"
    },
    {
        "question": "並木",
        "answer": "なみき"
    },
    {
        "question": "競馬",
        "answer": "けいば"
    },
    {
        "question": "永い",
        "answer": "ながい"
    },
    {
        "question": "測定",
        "answer": "そくてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "捜す",
        "answer": "さがす"
    },
    {
        "question": "北極",
        "answer": "ほっきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾燥",
        "answer": "かんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "定期券",
        "answer": "ていきけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "算盤",
        "answer": "そろばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "分布",
        "answer": "ぶんぷ"
    },
    {
        "question": "足袋",
        "answer": "たび"
    },
    {
        "question": "勇ましい",
        "answer": "いさましい"
    },
    {
        "question": "段階",
        "answer": "だんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "交替",
        "answer": "こうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "周辺",
        "answer": "しゅうへん"
    },
    {
        "question": "形容詞",
        "answer": "けいようし"
    },
    {
        "question": "包帯",
        "answer": "ほうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "清書",
        "answer": "せいしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "実績",
        "answer": "じっせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "弱点",
        "answer": "じゃくてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "清い",
        "answer": "きよい"
    },
    {
        "question": "形容動詞",
        "answer": "けいようどうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "蕎麦",
        "answer": "そば"
    },
    {
        "question": "延ばす",
        "answer": "のばす"
    },
    {
        "question": "割算",
        "answer": "わりざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "牧畜",
        "answer": "ぼくちく"
    },
    {
        "question": "採る",
        "answer": "とる"
    },
    {
        "question": "複数",
        "answer": "ふくすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "規律",
        "answer": "きりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "香水",
        "answer": "こうすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "着替え",
        "answer": "きがえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "改める",
        "answer": "あらためる"
    },
    {
        "question": "欧米",
        "answer": "おうべい"
    },
    {
        "question": "薄暗い",
        "answer": "うすぐらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "半島",
        "answer": "はんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "固い",
        "answer": "かたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "折角",
        "answer": "せっかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "比較的",
        "answer": "ひかくてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "団地",
        "answer": "だんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "腰掛ける",
        "answer": "こしかける"
    },
    {
        "question": "口紅",
        "answer": "くちべに"
    },
    {
        "question": "水平線",
        "answer": "すいへいせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "標準",
        "answer": "ひょうじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶岩",
        "answer": "ようがん"
    },
    {
        "question": "木材",
        "answer": "もくざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "雨戸",
        "answer": "あまど"
    },
    {
        "question": "課程",
        "answer": "かてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "毛皮",
        "answer": "けがわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "敬語",
        "answer": "けいご"
    },
    {
        "question": "井戸",
        "answer": "いど"
    },
    {
        "question": "傾らか",
        "answer": "なだらか"
    },
    {
        "question": "蛍光灯",
        "answer": "けいこうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "夕刊",
        "answer": "ゆうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "観測",
        "answer": "かんそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "照る",
        "answer": "てる"
    },
    {
        "question": "血液",
        "answer": "けつえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "衣食住",
        "answer": "いしょくじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "固まる",
        "answer": "かたまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "正門",
        "answer": "せいもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "文芸",
        "answer": "ぶんげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "終了",
        "answer": "しゅうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "承る",
        "answer": "うけたまわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "純粋",
        "answer": "じゅんすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "瀬戸物",
        "answer": "せともの"
    },
    {
        "question": "並行",
        "answer": "へいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "卒直",
        "answer": "そっちょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "領収",
        "answer": "りょうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "失恋",
        "answer": "しつれん"
    },
    {
        "question": "針金",
        "answer": "はりがね"
    },
    {
        "question": "拝見",
        "answer": "はいけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶かす",
        "answer": "とかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "名詞",
        "answer": "めいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "県庁",
        "answer": "けんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "流域",
        "answer": "りゅういき"
    },
    {
        "question": "停止",
        "answer": "ていし"
    },
    {
        "question": "枯れる",
        "answer": "かれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "分量",
        "answer": "ぶんりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "混ざる",
        "answer": "まざる"
    },
    {
        "question": "消毒",
        "answer": "しょうどく"
    },
    {
        "question": "述語",
        "answer": "じゅつご"
    },
    {
        "question": "漁師",
        "answer": "りょうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "不規則",
        "answer": "ふきそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "湿る",
        "answer": "しめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "曲線",
        "answer": "きょくせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "刺さる",
        "answer": "ささる"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷凍",
        "answer": "れいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "粒",
        "answer": "つぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "円周",
        "answer": "えんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗換",
        "answer": "のりかえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "間接",
        "answer": "かんせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "編む",
        "answer": "あむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "測量",
        "answer": "そくりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "幼児",
        "answer": "ようじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "零点",
        "answer": "れいてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "筆記",
        "answer": "ひっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "水滴",
        "answer": "すいてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "領事",
        "answer": "りょうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "換気",
        "answer": "かんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "憎い",
        "answer": "にくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "農産物",
        "answer": "のうさんぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "改札",
        "answer": "かいさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾杯",
        "answer": "かんぱい"
    },
    {
        "question": "清む",
        "answer": "すむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "掃く",
        "answer": "はく"
    },
    {
        "question": "接続",
        "answer": "せつぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "輸血",
        "answer": "ゆけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "編物",
        "answer": "あみもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "郵送",
        "answer": "ゆうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒸し暑い",
        "answer": "むしあつい"
    },
    {
        "question": "起床",
        "answer": "きしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "竹",
        "answer": "たけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "名刺",
        "answer": "めいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "紅葉",
        "answer": "こうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "干す",
        "answer": "ほす"
    },
    {
        "question": "座布団",
        "answer": "ざぶとん"
    },
    {
        "question": "床の間",
        "answer": "とこのま"
    },
    {
        "question": "省略",
        "answer": "しょうりゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "床屋",
        "answer": "とこや"
    },
    {
        "question": "政党",
        "answer": "せいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "枚数",
        "answer": "まいすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "方角",
        "answer": "ほうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "羽根",
        "answer": "はね"
    },
    {
        "question": "森林",
        "answer": "しんりん"
    },
    {
        "question": "防止",
        "answer": "ぼうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "超過",
        "answer": "ちょうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "増減",
        "answer": "ぞうげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "仲良し",
        "answer": "なかよし"
    },
    {
        "question": "録音",
        "answer": "ろくおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "憎む",
        "answer": "にくむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "応接",
        "answer": "おうせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "短期",
        "answer": "たんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "倉庫",
        "answer": "そうこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "甘やかす",
        "answer": "あまやかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "裏返す",
        "answer": "うらがえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶け込む",
        "answer": "とけこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉄橋",
        "answer": "てっきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "大層",
        "answer": "たいそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "輸送",
        "answer": "ゆそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "南極",
        "answer": "なんきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "往復",
        "answer": "おうふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "日課",
        "answer": "にっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "貯蔵",
        "answer": "ちょぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "預かる",
        "answer": "あずかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "童話",
        "answer": "どうわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "構造",
        "answer": "こうぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "皮肉",
        "answer": "ひにく"
    },
    {
        "question": "農村",
        "answer": "のうそん"
    },
    {
        "question": "薬缶",
        "answer": "やかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "温泉",
        "answer": "おんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "水蒸気",
        "answer": "すいじょうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "植木",
        "answer": "うえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "改めて",
        "answer": "あらためて"
    },
    {
        "question": "園芸",
        "answer": "えんげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "挟む",
        "answer": "はさむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "挟まる",
        "answer": "はさまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "濃度",
        "answer": "のうど"
    },
    {
        "question": "書籍",
        "answer": "しょせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "短編",
        "answer": "たんぺん"
    },
    {
        "question": "私鉄",
        "answer": "してつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "厚かましい",
        "answer": "あつかましい"
    },
    {
        "question": "快晴",
        "answer": "かいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒸発",
        "answer": "じょうはつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "地帯",
        "answer": "ちたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "新幹線",
        "answer": "しんかんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "電池",
        "answer": "でんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "気圧",
        "answer": "きあつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "編集",
        "answer": "へんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "醤油",
        "answer": "しょうゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "工芸",
        "answer": "こうげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "寝巻",
        "answer": "ねまき"
    },
    {
        "question": "停電",
        "answer": "ていでん"
    },
    {
        "question": "面接",
        "answer": "めんせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "照らす",
        "answer": "てらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "募集",
        "answer": "ぼしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "電柱",
        "answer": "でんちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "直線",
        "answer": "ちょくせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "寺院",
        "answer": "じいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "課税",
        "answer": "かぜい"
    },
    {
        "question": "人造",
        "answer": "じんぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "造船",
        "answer": "ぞうせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "引算",
        "answer": "ひきざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "海水浴",
        "answer": "かいすいよく"
    },
    {
        "question": "灯油",
        "answer": "とうゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "四季",
        "answer": "しき"
    },
    {
        "question": "著す",
        "answer": "あらわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "複写",
        "answer": "ふくしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "区切る",
        "answer": "くぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "液体",
        "answer": "えきたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "鈍い",
        "answer": "にぶい"
    },
    {
        "question": "境界",
        "answer": "きょうかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "群れ",
        "answer": "むれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "薄める",
        "answer": "うすめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "炭鉱",
        "answer": "たんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "接する",
        "answer": "せっする"
    },
    {
        "question": "子孫",
        "answer": "しそん"
    },
    {
        "question": "賞品",
        "answer": "しょうひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "瓶詰",
        "answer": "びんづめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "湯飲み",
        "answer": "ゆのみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "通貨",
        "answer": "つうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "普及",
        "answer": "ふきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "算数",
        "answer": "さんすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "耕地",
        "answer": "こうち"
    },
    {
        "question": "巻く",
        "answer": "まく"
    },
    {
        "question": "防犯",
        "answer": "ぼうはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "逆様",
        "answer": "さかさま"
    },
    {
        "question": "傾く",
        "answer": "かたむく"
    },
    {
        "question": "道順",
        "answer": "みちじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "超える",
        "answer": "こえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "刺身",
        "answer": "さしみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "内線",
        "answer": "ないせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "運河",
        "answer": "うんが"
    },
    {
        "question": "筆者",
        "answer": "ひっしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "湯気",
        "answer": "ゆげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "灯台",
        "answer": "とうだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "血圧",
        "answer": "けつあつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶く",
        "answer": "とく"
    },
    {
        "question": "混ぜる",
        "answer": "まぜる"
    },
    {
        "question": "憎らしい",
        "answer": "にくらしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "汚す",
        "answer": "よごす"
    },
    {
        "question": "長短",
        "answer": "ちょうたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "街角",
        "answer": "まちかど"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉄砲",
        "answer": "てっぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "巡査",
        "answer": "じゅんさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "片仮名",
        "answer": "かたかな"
    },
    {
        "question": "再三",
        "answer": "さいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "超す",
        "answer": "こす"
    },
    {
        "question": "為替",
        "answer": "かわせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "量る",
        "answer": "はかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "区分",
        "answer": "くぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "各自",
        "answer": "かくじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "各地",
        "answer": "かくち"
    },
    {
        "question": "功績",
        "answer": "こうせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "税関",
        "answer": "ぜいかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "四角",
        "answer": "しかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "将棋",
        "answer": "しょうぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "含める",
        "answer": "ふくめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "採点",
        "answer": "さいてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "涼む",
        "answer": "すずむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "規準",
        "answer": "きじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "敬う",
        "answer": "うやまう"
    },
    {
        "question": "毛糸",
        "answer": "けいと"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾かす",
        "answer": "かわかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "頭脳",
        "answer": "ずのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "逆さ",
        "answer": "さかさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "燃やす",
        "answer": "もやす"
    },
    {
        "question": "塩辛い",
        "answer": "しおからい"
    },
    {
        "question": "補う",
        "answer": "おぎなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "車庫",
        "answer": "しゃこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "浴衣",
        "answer": "ゆかた"
    },
    {
        "question": "再来週",
        "answer": "さらいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "電波",
        "answer": "でんぱ"
    },
    {
        "question": "武士",
        "answer": "ぶし"
    },
    {
        "question": "足跡",
        "answer": "あしあと"
    },
    {
        "question": "三角",
        "answer": "さんかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "田植え",
        "answer": "たうえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "順々",
        "answer": "じゅんじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶ける",
        "answer": "とける"
    },
    {
        "question": "祝日",
        "answer": "しゅくじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "湿度",
        "answer": "しつど"
    },
    {
        "question": "停車",
        "answer": "ていしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "破片",
        "answer": "はへん"
    },
    {
        "question": "温室",
        "answer": "おんしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "暴れる",
        "answer": "あばれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "乱暴",
        "answer": "らんぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "改造",
        "answer": "かいぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掘る",
        "answer": "ほる"
    },
    {
        "question": "専制",
        "answer": "せんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "歯磨き",
        "answer": "はみがき"
    },
    {
        "question": "育児",
        "answer": "いくじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "温帯",
        "answer": "おんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "針路",
        "answer": "しんろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "肯定",
        "answer": "こうてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "幼稚",
        "answer": "ようち"
    },
    {
        "question": "埋める",
        "answer": "うめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "短所",
        "answer": "たんしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "移転",
        "answer": "いてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "四捨五入",
        "answer": "ししゃごにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "直角",
        "answer": "ちょっかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "包装",
        "answer": "ほうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "貨物",
        "answer": "かもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "国籍",
        "answer": "こくせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "代名詞",
        "answer": "だいめいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "器械",
        "answer": "きかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "重量",
        "answer": "じゅうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "清掃",
        "answer": "せいそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "占う",
        "answer": "うらなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "副詞",
        "answer": "ふくし"
    },
    {
        "question": "執筆",
        "answer": "しっぴつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "材木",
        "answer": "ざいもく"
    },
    {
        "question": "高層",
        "answer": "こうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "列島",
        "answer": "れっとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "法則",
        "answer": "ほうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "要領",
        "answer": "ようりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "目印",
        "answer": "めじるし"
    },
    {
        "question": "混じる",
        "answer": "まじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "反省",
        "answer": "はんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "個所",
        "answer": "かしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "被せる",
        "answer": "かぶせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "灰色",
        "answer": "はいいろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉱物",
        "answer": "こうぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "接近",
        "answer": "せっきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "下線",
        "answer": "かせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "脱線",
        "answer": "だっせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "脂",
        "answer": "あぶら"
    },
    {
        "question": "看板",
        "answer": "かんばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "圧縮",
        "answer": "あっしゅく"
    },
    {
        "question": "片寄る",
        "answer": "かたよる"
    },
    {
        "question": "車輪",
        "answer": "しゃりん"
    },
    {
        "question": "区域",
        "answer": "くいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "戸棚",
        "answer": "とだな"
    },
    {
        "question": "湿気",
        "answer": "しっけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "片道",
        "answer": "かたみち"
    },
    {
        "question": "姓",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "符号",
        "answer": "ふごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "羊毛",
        "answer": "ようもう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掛け算",
        "answer": "かけざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "缶詰",
        "answer": "かんづめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "各々",
        "answer": "おのおの"
    },
    {
        "question": "姿勢",
        "answer": "しせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "四つ角",
        "answer": "よつかど"
    },
    {
        "question": "貝",
        "answer": "かい"
    },
    {
        "question": "仲直り",
        "answer": "なかなおり"
    },
    {
        "question": "幼稚園",
        "answer": "ようちえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "抽象",
        "answer": "ちゅうしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "講師",
        "answer": "こうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "凍える",
        "answer": "こごえる"
    }
]